Walter and Martha Leuba Prints SC.1988.02
ULS Archives & Special Collections
Walter and Martha Leuba Prints
1880-1969
ULS Archives & Special Collections
SC.1988.02
3000 items
- Known Artists, I.
  - A.E., John
    - Prints
      - Nirvana, (5 1/2 x 3 1/2")
        Scope and Content Notes
        Greeting card
  - ***********Abbe, Elfriede, 1919-2012
    - Prints
      - Chanterelles, (5 1/2 x 5 1/2")
        Signed woodcut
      - Inky Caps, (9 1/4 x 12")
        Signed wood engraving
      - Italian Cypress, (7 7/8 x 4 5/8")
        Greeting card, engraving
      - Season's Greetings, (4 3/4 x 5 1/2")
      - Season's Greetings, (5 x 6 7/8")
        Signed greeting card
      - Sheepfold, (5 x 7")
        Greeting card, wood engraving, writing inside
      - Snowflakes, (7 x 5 1/8")
        Greeting card, writing inside
      - Subject: 2 abstract wolves, (7 3/4 x 5")
      - Subject: Porcupine, (6 x 5 1/8")
    - Oversized Prints
    - Framed Prints
  - Abieg, H.R.
    - Prints, 1962
      - Chihuahuas, 1962; (8 x 16")
        Signed and matted xilograph, 3/25
  - Abrams, Ross
    - Prints, 1956
      - Mallorcan Terraces, 1956; (21 1/2 x 18")
        Signed and matter 5 color woodcut, 27/200
  - Ackermann, Helmut
    - Prints
      - Calendar of twelve images plus cover, (11 1/2 x 9")
        Signed woodcuts, 300/350
  - Adams, Tate
    - Prints, 1958-1969
      - Riders to the Sea, 1969; (11 7/16 x 15 7/16")
        Color woodcut, inside "Dolmein Editions, 1969"
      - Title page of "Alpha: The Mutabilities" (poems by Vincent McHugh), 1958; (11 1/2 x 17 1/2")
        Proof wood engraving
  - Adlard, H.
    - Prints
      - James Everette, (4 7/8 x 3 3/8")
        Engraving
  - Alexander, J.E.
    - Prints, 1962
      - Mountain Moor, 1962; (24 x 18")
        Signed 2 color woodcut, 97/210
  - Alexander, Nesbitt
    - Prints
      - "And it came to pass in those days,...", (5 x 7")
  - Alicea
    - Prints, 1962
      - Exposicion de ceramica de Amadeo Benet (Instituto de cultura puertorriquena), 1962; (18 x 29")
        Silkscreen, signed and matted poster
  - Alleyre, M.
    - Prints
      - Bocehoe, (5 x 7 1/4")
        Signed wood engraving, 3/50
  - Allinson, Adrian
    - Prints
      - Handeck Fall, (13 x 10")
        Signed wood engraving, 7/50
      - Winter, (13 1/4 x 10 1/2")
        Signed wood engraving, slightly foxed, 11/25
  - Amen, Irving
    - Prints
      - Einstein, ?
        Signed and framed woodcut, artist's proof
  - Angels, Valenti
    - Prints
      - Un Cavallino, (8 1/2 x 11 1/2")
        Signed linocut with paper cutout process, dedicated to Ben Braver
  - Ardizzone, Edward
    - Prints
      - Showmen and Suckers, (8 3/4 x 13 3/8")
  - Audubon, John J.
    - Prints
      - Cedar Bird, Bombycilla Carolinensis, (7 1/4 x 5 1/8")
  - **********Avetgn, John, Dávid Mária
    - Prints
      - Subject: Man carrying bag and weapon through trees, (6 7/16 x 4 1/4")
      - *******Subject: Man talking to woman on other side of fence through trees, (6 11/16 x 4 3/8")
        *********1 copy man and woman position switched
  - ************Azechi, Umetaro, 1947-1965
    - Prints, 1947-1965
      - August 1965 Calendar, Bird with Flowers, (8 1/8 x 5 1/8")
      - Rope, 1947; (9 3/4 x 15")
        Signed and matted woodcut, 57/100
      - Stand on the Snow Gorge, 1956; (22 x 28")
        Signed and framed woodcut, 114/200
  - Bac, Ferdinand
    - Prints
      - Yvette Guilbert, (15 3/8 x 11 5/16")
  - Bahle-Witting, Ilse, 1960
    - Prints, 1960
      - Subject: Harbor and Town, 1960; (23 1/4 x 16 1/2")
        Signed and unmatted lithograph, 29/100
  - Bailey
    - Prints
      - View of Arundel Castle, Sussex, England, (6 1/4 x 8 5/8")
        Color engraving
  - Ballinger, S., 1956
    - Prints, 1956
      - At Play, 1956; (22 x 17")
        Signed woodblock print, 71/210
  - Bank, Arnold
    - Prints
      - Exhibit Lounge Presents Alphabetic Calligraphics, (7 1/4 x 5 1/8")
  - Barlach, E.
    - Prints
      - Gruppe Im Sturm, (9 x 11 3/4")
        Woodcut, monogram in plate
  - Barone, L.C.
    - Prints
      - Chuck's Lane, (12 1/2 x 19")
        Signed woodcut, artist's proof
      - In Hand, (18 1/4 x 11 3/4")
        Signed 2 color woodcut, 32/40
  - Barton, Rick, 1960
    - Prints, 1960
      - Hands and Flowers #1/12, 1960; (11 1/4 x 16 1/4")
        Linocut
      - Hands and Flowers #2/12, 1960; (11 1/4 x 16 1/4")
      - Hands and Flowers #3/12, 1960; (11 1/4 x 16 1/4")
      - Hands and Flowers #4/12, 1960; (11 1/4 x 16 1/4")
      - Hands and Flowers #5/12, 1960; (11 1/4 x 16 1/4")
      - Hands and Flowers #6/12, 1960; (11 1/4 x 16 1/4")
      - Hands and Flowers #7/12, 1960; (11 1/4 x 16 1/4")
      - Hands and Flowers #8/12, 1960; (11 1/4 x 16 1/4")
      - Hands and Flowers #9/12, 1960; (11 1/4 x 16 1/4")
      - Hands and Flowers #10/12, 1960; (11 1/4 x 16 1/4")
      - Hands and Flowers #11/12, 1960; (11 1/4 x 16 1/4")
      - Hands and Flowers #12/12, 1960; (11 1/4 x 16 1/4")
      - A Modern Herbal, (6 x 9")
        Linocut, proof
  - *********Baskin, Leonard
    - Prints
      - *********(Subject?) Artist's Proof, (17 x 7 7/8")
        Wood engraving
      - Subject: Publication Announcement Re: William Blake, (6 x 14")
        Initialed wood engraving
  - *******Baskin, Leonard and Shahn, Ben
    - Prints
      - Beatitudes, (21 x 16")
        Signed and matted 4 color wood engraving, 67/400
  - Bates, Pervoe
    - Prints
      - The Pheasants, (15 1/4 x 13")
        Signed woodcut, 4/100
  - ********Baumann, Gustave, 1932-1948
    - Prints, 1932-1948
      - Church-Rancho De Taos, 1948; (17 x 13 1/2")
        Framed, signed, and stamped multicolor woodcut; 98/125
      - ********An Eagle Ceremony at Tesuque Pueblo, 1932; ********
        Woodcut, stamp in place, 1/3000
      - Rio Tesuque, 1946; (17 x 13 1/2")
        Signed and matted multicolor woodcut, 69/125
  - Bawden, B.
    - Prints
      - Reverie, (9 1/4 x 7 3/4")
        Steel engraving, initaled in plate
      - Turtle in Box, (9 1/8 x 8 1/4")
        Steel engraving, signed in plate
  - Bellezze, Bernardino
    - Prints
      - Leonardo the Florentine, Subject: Florence, (18 x 12")
        Woodcut
  - ******Bellows
    - Prints
      - Subject: Miss Katherine Rosen, (5 1/2 x 4 1/8")
      - *********Subject: Waldo Peirce, *********
  - ***Berwick, John
    - Prints
      - ****In Duris Servata Fides, ******
  - Bezombes, Roger
    - Prints
      - Algerian Woman, (11 x 16")
        Lithograph, reproduction
  - Bianco, Pamela
    - Prints
      - Three Fairy Tales, (8 1/8 x 5 1/2")
        A letter is accompanied in the sleeve
  - Bieryer, S.L.
    - Prints
      - Fish, (21 x 15")
        Signed etching, 50/100
  - Bindon
    - Prints
      - Dean Swift, aged about 65, (6 1/8 x 4 1/4")
  - Bishop, J. and Weigall, C.H.
    - Prints
      - Bees, Plate 70, (6 x 9 1/2")
        Colored engraving, poor condition
      - Birds, Plate 53, (6 x 9 1/2")
      - Birds, Plate 59, (6 x 9 1/2")
  - Bliss, Douglas Percy
    - Prints
      - From Rasselas, (5 1/2 x 8")
      - From Rasselas, (6 x 8")
      - From Rasselas, (6 1/8 x 8")
      - Tam O'Shanter, (6 1/2 x 5 1/4")
      - Tapping a Steel Furnace, (8 x 5 1/2")
        Signed and matted wood engraving
  - Bo, Lars
    - Prints
      - A Book of Love Poems, (9 7/16 x 21 5/16")
  - Boehmer, G.G.
    - Prints
      - The Tower, (15 1/4 x 8 1/4")
  - Boltraffio, Giovanni Antonio
    - Prints
      - Portrait of a Youth, (5 1/2 x 3 1/2")
  - *********Bone/Bonne, Stephen
    - Prints
      - Animal Auction, (5 x 7 1/2")
      - Men on Merry-Go-Round, (7 x 4 1/2")
        Wood engraving, proof with foxing
  - Borodin, A.V.
    - Prints
      - In the North, An Old Huntsman, (25 x 17")
  - Bostelmann, Else
    - Prints
      - A Family to Raise, (6 1/8 x 4 1/2")
  - Bostock, James
    - Prints
      - Azaleas, (7 x 10")
      - Brentford Lock, (7 x 10")
      - Cactus Garden, (10 x 12")
        Signed wood engraving proof
      - Green Grocer's, (7 x 10")
      - Sentimental Journey, (7 1/4 x 10")
      - Winter Sunset, (21 x 17")
        Signed and matted multicolored wood engraving
  - Botticelli
    - Prints
      - Head of Christ, (5 3/4 x 4")
      - Head of the Resurrected Christ, (5 3/4 x 3 13/16")
  - Boucher
    - Prints
      - Subject: 2 children talking in garden, (7 x 5")
      - Subject: 2 men waiting outside while one man knocks on door, (7 x 5")
      - Subject: 2 men walking with child beggar beside, (7 x 5")
        2 copies, one brown ink, one grey
      - Subject: Carriage of two women being pulled by two horses and accompanied by man on horse riding alongside, (7 x 5")
      - Subject: Crowd of people near buildings at night, (7 x 5")
      - Subject: Hunter talking to group of people and dog, (7 x 5")
      - Subject: Man approaching woman holding rope in bedroom, (7 x 5")
      - Subject: Man helping woman into carriage, (7 x 5")
      - Subject: Man outside store. Store has picture of animal and man playing game., (7 x 5")
      - Subject: Man reading against tree while another man sells books on ground, (7 x 5")
      - Subject: Man showing old woman pair of shoes, (7 x 5")
      - Subject: Man talking to woman sitting on chair and woman standing, (7 x 5")
      - Subject: Woman carrying food cart in city, (7 x 5")
      - Subject: Woman sleeping in chair in corner of room with window open, (7 x 5")
      - Subject: Woman talking to man over counter with separate man standing in corner, (7 x 5")
  - Bowman, Heath and Dickinson, Stirling
    - Prints
      - Market in San Miguel, (8 3/4 x 5 3/4")
  - ********Boyd, Fiske, 1951
    - Prints, 1951
      - Concept, (17 x 12 1/16")
      - Untitled, Subject: abstracted cityscape (U.N. building), 1951; (10 1/2 x 14 1/2")
        Signed wood engraving, 1/100
  - Braby, Dorothea, 1948-1953
    - Prints, 1948-1953
      - Gentleman at Restaurant, (6 5/8 x 8")
        Signed two color wood engraving
      - Imabinogion, 1948; (5 1/2 x 9 1/4")
        Wood engraving and text, 1/550
      - Man and Woman with fan, 1953; (6 5/8 x 8")
      - Man with cigarette, Portrait of woman with fan, 1953; (6 5/8 x 8")
      - Seven 2 color wood engravings: 1) The Rivals, 2) Courtship, 3)The Baby, 4) Misunderstanding, 5) The Quarrel, 6) Scandal, 7) Untitled, Subject: Cupid with silhouettes, (6 x 8 1/4")
        Signed, 7/20
      - Two men at Sphinx, 1953; (6 5/8 x 8")
      - Woman with Jewel case, Gentleman on sofa, 1953; (6 5/8 x 8")
      - Woman with parasol, woman seated, 1953; (6 5/8 x 8")
  - Braque, George
    - Prints
      - Subject: 2 fish on plate with lemon, (4 1/8 x 5 3/4")
  - ***************Bresslern-Roth, Norbertine
    - Prints
      - Lion, (10 1/4 x 9 3/4")
        Signed and unmatted colored woodcut
      - Tiger Cub, (11 1/4 x 9")
        Signed and unmatted woodcut
      - Two Squirrels, (8 1/2 x 7")
        Signed multicolor woodcut
  - ********Brett, Oliver
    - Prints
      - ********Vicimus, *************
  - Bridges, James
    - Prints
      - Stonehenge, Wiltshire, (6 1/4 x 8 5/8")
        Watercolor
  - Bringer, Helen
    - Prints
      - Subject: Woman reading, (8 x 5 1/2")
  - Brocquy, Louis Le, 1969
    - Prints, 1969
      - The Tain, 1969; (11 1/4 x 14 3/4")
        Brush drawings, inside "Dolmein Editions, 1969"
  - Bronzino
    - Prints
      - Lodovico Capponi, (5 1/2 x 3 1/2")
      - Venus, Cupid, Folly, and Time, (5 x 4")
  - Brown, Harold Haven
    - Prints
      - City Gates to Paiel De Var, So. France, (7 x 9")
        Signed multicolored linocut
      - Saint Chapell, (8 7/16 x 8 1/2")
        Signed colored woodcut
  - Brussel-Smith, Bernard, 1945-1963
    - Prints, 1945-1963
      - Giambattista Bodoni, (6 1/4 x 8 1/4")
      - Gutenberg, (6 1/2 x 8")
      - Gutenberg, 1945; (6 1/2 x 8")
      - Rudolph Kock, (7 1/2 x 9")
        Wood engraving, signed twice
      - Self Portrait, 1963; (6 1/2 x 9 1/2")
  - ***********Bryce, Helen B.
    - Prints
      - *******Bibury Mill, **********
        Wood engraving, greeting card
      - Cocklands Press, Burford, Oxford, (4 1/4 x 5 3/4")
  - *******Bryden, R., 1899
    - Prints, 1899
      - Some Woodcuts of Men of Letters of the 19th Century, 1899; (23 x 18")
        Woodcut, title page of series of [12] woodcuts of 19th century authors
      - Some Woodcuts of Men of Letters of the 19th Century: Alfred, Lord Tennyson, 1899; (23 x 18")
        Woodcut, portrait of Alfred, Lord Tennyson
      - ***********Some Woodcuts of Men of Letters of the 19th Century: Count Leo Tolstoi (Tolstoy?), 1899; (23 x 18")
        *********Woodcut, portrait of Leo Tolstoi (Tolstoy?)
      - Some Woodcuts of Men of Letters of the 19th Century: Heinrik Ibsen, 1899; (23 x 18")
        Woodcut, portrait of Heinrik Ibsen
      - Some Woodcuts of Men of Letters of the 19th Century: John Ruskin, 1899; (23 x 18")
        Woodcut, portrait of John Ruskin
      - Some Woodcuts of Men of Letters of the 19th Century: Ralph Waldo Emerson, 1899; (23 x 18")
        Woodcut, portrait of Ralph Waldo Emerson
      - Some Woodcuts of Men of Letters of the 19th Century: Robert Browning, 1899; (23 x 18")
        Woodcut, portrait of Robert Browning
      - Some Woodcuts of Men of Letters of the 19th Century: Robert Louis Stevenson, 1899; (23 x 18")
        Woodcut, portrait of Robert Louis Stevenson
      - Some Woodcuts of Men of Letters of the 19th Century: Rudyard Kipling, 1899; (23 x 18")
        Woodcut, portrait of Rudyard Kipling
      - Some Woodcuts of Men of Letters of the 19th Century: Thomas Carlyle, 1899; (23 x 18")
        Woodcut, portrait of Thomas Carlyle
      - Some Woodcuts of Men of Letters of the 19th Century: Victor Hugo, 1899; (23 x 18")
        Woodcut, portrait of Victor Hugo
      - Some Woodcuts of Men of Letters of the 19th Century: Walt Whitman, 1899; (23 x 18")
        Woodcut, portrait of Walt Whitman
      - Some Woodcuts of Men of Letters of the 19th Century: William Morris, 1899; (23 x 18")
        Woodcut, portrait of William Morris
  - *******Buchholz, Wolff
    - Prints
      - ********Subject: Mountain Range?, (23 1/2 x 16 1/4")
        Signed woodblock print, multi-printed, 63/100
  - Buday, George, 1937
    - Prints, 1937
      - Last Supper, 1937; (7 1/2 x 10 1/2")
  - Buff, Conrad
    - Prints
      - Subject: Do, (5 x 6 1/2")
  - Buren, Martijntje
    - Prints
      - From the Books of..., (2 x 2 1/2")
  - Burnshaw, Stanley
    - Prints
      - The Body Makes the Minde, (9 3/4 x 6 7/8")
        Story
  - Butler, Pierce
    - Prints
      - A Memorial Address, (7 3/4 x 5 1/4")
  - Carter, Bruce
    - Prints
      - "War Requiem" poster
  - Evans, Henry, 1918-1990
    - Prints
  - Frasconi, Antonio, 1919-2013
    - Prints
  - O'Connor, John
    - Prints, 1927-1939
      - Cornwall, 1927; 1.; (9 x 13 1/2)
        Signed multi color wood engraving, 5/25
      - Ivy and Tree, 1939; 2.; (15 1/2 x 17 1/2)
        Signed and matted colored engraving, 1/10
  - Odle, Allen
    - Prints
      - The Gypsy - A new quarterly, (11 5/8 x 9 1/16")
  - O'Hara, Frederick
    - Prints
      - Riders, (24 x 17 1/4")
        Signed and matted woodblock print, 71/210
  - O'Higgins, Pablo, 1904-1983
    - Prints
      - Brick-Makers, 1950
  - Olson, Janet
    - Prints, 1959
      - Orange bird, 1959; (17 x 32 1/2")
        Signed and matted woodcut, 4/20
  - Outmarao
    - Prints, 1955
      - Six reproductions - Serial printed in France, 1955; (18 1/2 x 13 1/4")
  - Pal
    - Prints
      - Grand ballet brighton, (15 3/8 x 11 5/16")
  - Parker, Agnes Miller
    - Prints, 1920-1937
      - Ant and fly, 1931; (7 3/4 x 10 1/4")
      - Barbary sheep, 1920; (10 3/8 x 8")
      - Bison, 1929; (8 1/8 x 7")
      - Fish, 1930; (7 x 8 1/4")
      - Fox and stork, 1931; (7 3/4 x 10 1/4")
      - Iris, barweed, and rushes, 1937; (11 1/2 x 13 1/2")
        Framed and matted wood engraving, 13/35
      - Jane and roderick, (8 1/4 x 7 1/8")
      - March hare, 1937; (8 x 5 1/4")
      - Sauve qui peut, 1934; (5 3/8 x 8 3/8")
        Signed and matted wood engraving, 2/35
      - Tree fruits, 1936; (7 x 8 1/4")
      - Subject: Man with cane overlooking landscape, (6 1/8 x 9 1/2")
      - Weasel, 1935; (7 x 8 1/4")
  - Parker, Stephen
    - Prints
      - Drawings, (14 x 8 1/2")
      - Subject: Drawings and grapics, (13 1/2 x 10")
  - Patown, John
    - Prints
      - James thomson, (7 1/4 x 4 3/4")
  - Patterson, Frank
    - Prints
      - Julius gold - Musical authority, (15 3/8 x 10 1/4")
  - Pears, Tom
    - Prints
      - Bewick, (3 3/4 x 4 7/8")
        Card for George Nama
      - Christmas greeting card, (5 1/4 x 4")
  - Pellew, Claughton
    - Prints
      - The Dead tree, (6 x 7 1/2")
        Signed wood engraving with severe foxxing, 2/50
      - The River, (6 7/8 x 8 1/2")
  - Penguin Prints
    - Prints
      - Penguin Prints, (10 1/2 x 14")
        Set of 11 offset lithographies, we have #1, 2, 5, 9-11
  - Pepler, Ditchling
    - Prints
      - In nativiate domini, (19 2/8 x 15 1/8")
  - Peterson, Ann
    - Prints
      - Subject: Flowers, (4 1/2 x 4")
        Valentines card with writing inside
  - Peterson, Norton
    - Prints, 1969
      - Eight sketches of Pittsburgh, (17 x 15")
        Offset lithograph
      - Hunt bontanical library, (4 x 3 1/8")
        We have two copies and one is signed
      - Huren building, (8 3/4 x 22 3/4")
        Signed and matted woodcut
      - First specimen sheet, (6 3/8 x 4 3/8")
      - Greetings, (6 x 4")
        Signed, we have 2 copies
      - Jiggs, (8 3/4 x 6 1/4")
      - Matthew Stevenson's "Twelve months", (5 1/2 x 4 3/4")
      - Subject: Animal face design, (5 9/16 x 4 3/8")
      - Subject: Arichectural piece, (9 3/4 x 6")
      - Subject: Black and red design, (5 1/2 x 4 1/4")
        Card
      - Subject: City buildings, (9 3/4 x 6")
      - Subject: Design, (6 1/8 x 4 3/8")
      - Subject: Doorknob, (9 3/4 x 6")
      - Subject: Goose, (9 3/4 x 6")
      - Subject: Lion statue, (6 3/16 x 5 5/8")
        Signed
      - Subject: Party viewed through architectural doorway, 1969; (12 x 15 3/4")
        Orignial pen and ink
      - Subject: Man holding bottle, (9 3/4 x 6")
      - Subject: Monkey sitting on melon, (9 3/4 x 6")
      - Subject: Naked man with missing limbs, (9 3/4 x 6")
      - Subject: Tree, (9 1/4 x 12 1/4")
        Etching
      - Subject: Underside of car, (9 3/4 x 6")
  - Peterson, Norton and Ann
    - Prints
      - Subject: Abstract white cubes, (5 7/8 x 4")
        Card, we have two signed copies, one is in an envelope
      - Subject: Dragon and lion, (3 3/4 x 5 1/8")
        Christmas card
      - Subject: Lion with wings, (4 3/8 x 5 6/8")
        Seasons greetings card with writing inside
      - Subject: Two lions around tree, (5 3/8 x 3 3/8")
  - Pett, Abigail
    - Prints
      - Subject: Deer, (5 1/2 x 3 1/2")
  - Petts, John
    - Prints
      - Aberdaron, Caernaryvonshire, (5 x 6 1/4")
        Wood engraving greeting card
      - Cwm Eigiau, North Wales, (5 x 6 1/4")
        Wood engraving card
      - Head of the roman steps, ardudwy, (5 x 6 1/4")
  - Pierce, Danny
    - Prints, 1953
      - In the fields #2, (20 x 16")
        Signed and matted print woodblock, 26/210
  - Pierce, Leona
    - Prints
      - High swing, (12 x 14 3/4")
        Signed and matted multicolor woodcut, 3/6
  - Pilkington, Margaret
    - Prints, 1928-1931
      - Mountain village, 1928; (8 x 10 1/2")
        Signed wood engraving, 8/25
      - Village scene, 1931; (10 1/4 x 8")
        Wood engraving, 1/30
  - Piper, John
    - Prints
      - Hambledon hill, Dorset England, (6 1/4 x 8 5/8")
        Water color
  - Piranesi, Giovanni Battista
    - Prints
      - Carceri invenzioni, (15 13/16 x 119/16")
        Wood engraving, number 5 of series
      - Il Camp marzio dell'antica roma, (11 11/16 x 15 7/8")
        Wood engraving, number 20 of series
      - Il Camp marzio dell'antica roma, (11 5/8 x 16")
        Wood engraving, number 23 of the series
      - Le Antichita romane, (11 3/4 x 16 1/16")
        Wood engraving, number 22 of series
      - Untitled, (16 x 11 5/8")
        Wood engraving, number 36 of series
  - Pisanello
    - Prints
      - Subject: Dog with muzzle, (3 13/16 x 4 3/8")
  - Pissarro, Lucien
    - Prints
      - Hillside, (5 1/2 x 8 5/8")
        Signed via monogram wood engraving
      - Subject: Mother and child gathering firewood in a forest, (6 3/5 x 8 3/4")
        Framed multicolor woodcut proof
      - Young girl picking flowers, (4 3/8 x 4 1/2")
        Colored wood engraving
  - Pitkin, Charles W.
    - Prints
      - In defense of books, (15 1/16 x 9 3/8")
  - Plummer, Charles
    - Prints
      - Les Plumes de dieu sont mon ecu, (5 x 3 1/2")
  - Pohl, Alfred
    - Prints
      - Stadt, (22 1/2 x 17 1/2")
        Signed black and white woodcut, 21/100
  - Popham, A.E. and Penwick, K. M.
    - Prints
      - The National gallery of Canada, (11 x 8 1/2")
  - Pol, John de
    - Prints
      - Faneuil Hall, Boston, (11 x 8 3/8")
      - Noah Webster, (11 x 8 1/8")
      - The Portland head lighthouse, (11 x 8 3/8")
  - Pollard and Moss
    - Prints, 1880
      - A Haunting turn out in the peninsula, 1880; (Image: 10 6 1/2")
        Colored lithograph
  - Praetorius, C. J.
    - Prints
      - The Desborough mirror, (8 5/8 x 6 1/4")
  - Prendergast, James
    - Prints
      - Young American artist, (6 11/16 x 4 1/4")
  - Price, Julius
    - Prints
      - An Arist's model, (15 3/8 x 11 5/16")
  - Pym, Roland
    - Prints
      - Lacock Abbey, Wiltshire England, (6 1/4 x 8 5/8")
  - Quick, Hilda
    - Prints, 1933
      - Dandelion, 1933; (6 3/4 x 8")
  - Quick, Robert
    - Prints, 1958
      - A Portfolio of birds, 1958; (11 x 15")
        Have a set of twelve
      - A Portfolio of cats, (9 1/2 x 12")
        Have two prints in portfolio
  - RA, Opie
    - Prints
      - The Reverand Sammuel Parr L.L.D., (4 1/2 x 4 1/8")
  - Raschent, H.
    - Prints
      - A Franklin keepsake, (16 15/16 x 10 3/8")
  - Rassenfosse, Armand
    - Prints
      - Grande brasserie Van Velsen freres Bornhiem, (11 5/16 x 15 3/8")
  - Ratberer, Mary
    - Prints
      - Subject: Abstract, (5 1/8 x 4 1/8")
  - Rather, Lois
    - Prints
      - Lovely Isadora, (7 1/16 x 17")
        Pamphlet
  - Raverat, Gwendolen
    - Prints, 1930
      - Chesnut trees, Grantchester, (4 1/2 x 3 1/4")
      - Daphni's pipes, (5 x 2 1/2")
      - Duck pond, (4 3/4 x 5 1/4")
      - Lambingfold, (4 1/2 x 7")
        Wood engraving with some foxing in the lower portion
      - Low shore, (5 1/2 x 5")
      - The Millpond, (7 x 5")
      - The Mole, (6 x 8 1/2")
        Wood engraving with marks from plate
      - Old people, (6 x 5")
      - The Roding, (5 1/2 x 7 1/2")
      - Time and tide, 1930; (Image: 4 x 2 1/2")
        Eight wood engravings
      - Trout stream, (5 x 5 1/2")
      - The Ver, (6 x 8 1/2")
      - Winter evening, (5 1/4 x 5 1/2")
  - Ravilious, Eric
    - Prints
      - Aquarious, (5 x 6 1/2")
      - Birds in garden carriage, (5 1/2 x 7 3/4")
      - Chanticleer, (13 1/2 x 11 1/2")
      - Gemini, (4 3/4 x 6 3/8")
      - The importunate ass, (6 1/2 x 5")
      - June, (5 5/8 x 3 5/7")
      - From: atrocities of the pirated by Aron Smith, (5 5/8 x 3 5/8")
      - From: the hansom cab and the pigeons by L.A.G. Strong, (6 1/2 x 5")
      - The Wood engravings of Eric Ravilious, (16 1/2 x 23 7/16")
  - Rawlins, Monica
    - Prints, 1925
      - The Scarecrow, 1925; (7 1/2 x 8 1/4")
        Signed wood engraving, 5/25
  - Reed, Philip
    - Prints, 1936
      - Subject: Dicken's character, 1936; (16 x 20 3/4")
  - Reisch, G.
    - Prints
      - The House of learning, (6 3/16 x 4 5/16")
  - Rembrandt
    - Prints
      - A Girl with a broom, (5 1/2 x 3 1/2")
      - Self-portrait, (5 1/2 x 3 1/2")
      - A Woman holding a pink, (5 1/2 x 3 1/2")
  - Renton, Michael
    - Prints, 1965